<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<resources>
  <string name="action_help">Help</string>
  <string name="app_name">Turbo Download</string>
  <string name="conn_charging_warning">Downloading via mobile networks may result in additional charges depending.</string>
  <string name="conn_notice_detail">To enable Turbo Download, both WLAN and Mobile data must be turned on.</string>
  <string name="conn_notice_title">Either Mobile or WLAN is OFF.</string>
  <string name="connection_mobile">Mobile data</string>
  <string name="connection_wlan">WLAN</string>
  <string name="enable_switch_off">Off</string>
  <string name="enable_switch_on">On</string>
  <string name="hetcomm_help">&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Turbo Download Help&lt;/u&gt; &lt;/h1&gt;&lt;br&gt;Download large files at top speed by using WLAN and 4G/3G at the same time. &lt;h4&gt;1. Go to Settings and tap Turbo Download.&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;h4&gt;2. Tap the switch to turn on Turbo Download.&lt;/h4&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;[Tip]&lt;/b&gt; To speed up download if connected to both WLAN and 4G/3G at the start of your download. &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;[Tip]&lt;/b&gt; If your WLAN or 4G/3G connection is too slow, you can use your faster network connection to download. &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;[Tip]&lt;/b&gt; Speed and performance of Turbo Download may be affected network environment while downloading. &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- If the signals are unstable, the speed and performance of this feature may be affected. &lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- however, on the average, download speed will be doubled than compared to using only WLAN or 4G/3G alone. &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;[Tip]&lt;/b&gt; When the speed difference of WLAN and 4G/3G is large(Normally 2.5 times), the Turbo Download will stop or will not support to avoid getting bad performance with regard to speed. &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;[Tip]&lt;/b&gt; The Turbo Download would be disabled automatically once Tethering/Vpn is turned on. &lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="hetcomm_intro">Download large files(over 20 MB) faster using WLAN and 4G/3G networks at the same time. The Turbo Download icon will be shown on the status bar when it is running. To use Turbo Download, both WLAN and Mobile data must be turned on. When it is enabled, any application data that your have selected to download via WLAN only will be downloaded via WLAN and 4G/3G networks anyway.</string>
  <string name="hotknotbeam_saved_location">beam</string>
  <string name="network_Mobile">3/4G</string>
  <string name="network_WiFi">WLAN</string>
  <string name="notify_top_title">Download Accelerator</string>
  <string name="ratio_is_back">Turbo download reuse WLAN and Mobile data together to download files.</string>
  <string name="ratio_is_single">WLAN/Mobile data speed is slow. To speed up the download, Turbo download will only use Mobile data/WLAN to download files.</string>
  <string name="turn_off_due_to_roaming">Turbo Download is OFF due to Roaming</string>
  <string name="turn_off_due_to_shutdown">Turbo Download is OFF due to Shutdown</string>
  <string name="turn_off_due_to_tether">Turbo Download is OFF due to Tethering ON</string>
  <string name="turn_off_due_to_vpn">Turbo Download is OFF due to Vpn ON</string>
  <string name="turn_on">Turn on %1$s</string>
  <string name="unit_Mbps">Mbps</string>
</resources>
